ı	Programming	Technical	Interpersonal	Tools	Techniques
Key Skills	R	Requirements Analysis	Team Management	Basic OpenCV	Topic Modelling
	Basic C++	Business Context &	reei	R-HBase	Sentiment Mining
	Basic Java	Problem Definition	Counselling 1	PERT	Support Vector Machines

Business Analyst, Innovation Labs

Mu Sigma Business Solutions

Talent Quest

September 2012 - Present 1 year

My work in Mu Sigma involves Analytics Research and Product Design, and is focused at information retrieval and visualization from large volume unstructured sources like twitter, text response surveys, resume databases etc. I use algorithms like LDA, SVM etc and tools like HBase to store and extract meaningful information from text data. I also work in the field of Computer Vision and the Internet of things, with focus on real time object detection from streaming video feeds and controlling physical installations (e.g. Doors, Lighting, AC etc) based on the information from the same. I manage a team of three people working towards creating product prototypes in the field.

Research Associate, Recruitments Consulting

June 2012 - August 2012 3 months

My work in Talent Quest involved Executive Search and Consulting Services to companies for various profiles, in mid- and senior management positions. I worked across domains and groups including The Oberoi Group and The Marriott Group in Hospitality, Towers-Watson in BFSI, Max Ventures, CVENT India and Rhythm Corner Associates.

Internships

Work Experience

Trainee Requitement Analyst May 2011 - December 2011 8 months

TechEpsilon Software

Statistical Quality Assurance Intern January 2012 - April 2012 4 months Perfetti Van Melle India

Industrial Research Trainee December 2009 1 month **Ranbaxy Research Labs**

Education

Bachelor of Engineering - Biotechnology August 2008 - May 2012 4 years **Manipal Institute of Technology**

AISSCE 2008 April 2008

Delhi Public School, Vasant Kunj, New Delhi

Eeshan Chatterjee | Citizenship: Indian | Date of Birth: August 9, 1990

http://www.linkedin.com/pub/eeshan-chatterjee/33/b47/969

A-323, Mahaveer Tuscan Apartments, Basavana nagar Main Road, Near Hoodi Circle, Whitefield, Bangalore, 560066.